export const popcultureData = [
    {
        id: 1,
        type: "multiple choice",
        question: "‘XO Tour Lif3’ & the ‘Futsal Shuffle’ are songs belonging to which rapper?",
        options: ["Rae Sremmurd", "Lil Uzi Vert", "Lil Yachty", "Trippie Red"],
        answer: "Rae Sremmurd",
        region:'U.S.A',
        description: `Rae Sremmurd - pronounced "Ray-Shrim-er," consis.ting of real life brothers Slim Jxmmi and Swae Lee.`
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        type: "multiple choice",
        question: "This two-time Academy award winner and three-time Screen Guild Award winner is famous for his many dynamic roles, including starring in ‘Moonlight’ & as Colonel Boggs in ‘The Hunger Games’",
        options: ["Mershala Ali", "Wesley Snipes", "Idris Alba", "Forest Whitaker"],
        answer: "Mershala Ali",
        region:'U.S.A',
        description: `He became the only black actor since Denzel Washington to earn two Oscars.`
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        type: "multiple choice",
        question: "Which AfroBeats-Alte artist featured on Wizkid’s “Essence” from his Made in Lagos album?",
        options: ["Burna Boy", "Tems", "Davido", "Mayorkun"],
        answer: "Tems",
        region:'Nigeria',
        description: `As a youngster, Tems adored Beyoncé and Destiny’s Child; she felt fretfulness and powerful urge to sing. At age 11, she began to prepare her voice to truly get into music.`
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        type: "multiple choice",
        question: "Which UK musical group dropped the hits “Options”, “Lupita” and “Kate Winslet” in 2020?",
        options: ["NSG", "Krept & Konan", "Young T & Bugsey", "Coldplay"],
        answer: "NSG",
        region:'U.K.',
        description: `The six-piece act is part of a wave of artists fusing grime, road rap, bashment, and afrobeats into what is quickly becoming the effervescent sound of Britain’s youth.`
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        type: "multiple choice",
        question: "Drake has collaborated with all the following UK Grime artists except for who?",
        options: ["Stormzy", "Skepta", "Darkoo", "Wiley"],
        answer: "Darkoo",
        region:'Nigeria/U.K.',
        description:`She began to merge the influences of being in the UK with the sound of her favourite African artists like WizKid and Maleek Berry, leading her to release her debut single ‘Gas Station’ at the tender age of 16`
    },
    {
        id: 6,
        type: "multiple choice",
        question: "Which popular rap artist played “Modie” in the UK show Top Boy?",
        options: ["Santan Dave", "Kano", "AJ Tracey", "J Hus"],
        answer: "Santan Dave",
        region:'U.K.',
        description: `Dave made his debut appearance on Black Box, a YouTube channel for freestyle rap, in May 2015.`
    },
    {
        id: 7,
        type: "multiple choice",
        question: "Idris Elba was NOT a part of this movie.",
        options: ["The Jungle Book", "Daddy’s Girls", "Obsessed", "The Wire"],
        answer: "The Wire",
        region:'U.S.A',
        description: ``
    },
    {
        id: 8,
        type: "multiple choice",
        question: "The following popular shows are based on books/comics/manga except for?",
        options: ["The Walking Dead", "Hunter x Hunter", "Lupin", "Stranger Things"],
        answer: "Stranger Things",
        region:'U.S.A',
        description: ``
    },
    {
        id: 9,
        type: "multiple choice",
        question: "This popular crime show did not stop filming in 2020?",
        options: ["Law & Order: SVU", "Criminal Minds", "NCIS", "How to Get Away With Murder"],
        answer: "Law & Order: SVU",
        region:'U.S.A',
        description: ``
    },
    {
        id: 10,
        type: "multiple choice",
        question: "Tupac Shakur went to what school?",
        options: ["Julliard", "Baltimore School of Performing Arts", "Berkeley College", "Performing Arts and Technology"],
        answer: "Baltimore School of Performing Arts",
        region:'U.S.A',
        description: ``
    },
    {
        id: 11,
        type: "multiple choice",
        question: "What are the names of Kim Kardashian and Kanye West’s kids?",
        options: ["North, Sir, China and Sam", "Dakota, Saint, Sarah, and Justice", "North, Saint, Chicago and Psalm", "North, Hope, Brooklyn, and Psalm"],
        answer: "North, Saint, Chicago and Psalm",
        region:'U.S.A',
        description: ``
    },
    {
        id: 12,
        type: "multiple choice",
        question: "What is the name of Michelle Obama’s 2018 memoir?",
        options: ["Becoming", "Acts of a True Lady", "Michelle Obama", "Finally First Lady"],
        answer: "Becoming",
        region:'U.S.A',
        description: ``
    },
    {
        id: 13,
        type: "multiple choice",
        question: "Which actor voiced both Darth Vader and The Lion King’s Mufasa?",
        options: ["Keith David", "Dennis Haysbert", "James Earl Jones", "Morgan Freeman"],
        answer: "James Earl Jones",
        region:'U.S.A',
        description: ``
    },
    {
        id: 14,
        type: "multiple choice",
        question: "What modern-day item made a cameo in the final season of Game of Thrones?",
        options: ["a car", "an iPhone", "a jet", "A Starbucks cup"],
        answer: "A Starbucks cup",
        region:'U.S.A',
        description: ``
    },
    {
        id: 15,
        type: "multiple choice",
        question: "What does the acronym “smh” stand for?",
        options: ["Stop my horse", "Shaking my hips", "Shaking my head", "Shout my honor"],
        answer: "Shaking my head",
        region:'U.S.A',
        description: ``
    },
    {
        id: 16,
        type: "multiple choice",
        question: "Who sings the song “Say so” that’s behind the popular TikTok dance?",
        options: ["Saweetie", "Doja Cat", "City Girls", "Megan Thee Stallion"],
        answer: "Doja Cat",
        region:'U.S.A',
        description: ``
    },
    {
        id: 17,
        type: "multiple choice",
        question: "What day is Star Wars day?",
        options: ["May 5", "Sept 6", "May 4", "April 3"],
        answer: "May 4",
        region:'U.S.A',
        description: ``
    },
    {
        id: 18,
        type: "multiple choice",
        question: "Which pop star is the godmother to both of Elton John’s sons?",
        options: ["Lady Gaga", "Adele", "Drew Barrymore", "Celine Dion"],
        answer: "Lady Gaga",
        region:'U.S.A',
        description: ``
    },
    {
        id: 19,
        type: "multiple choice",
        question: "What is Rihanna’s full name?",
        options: ["Raven Fenty", "Rihanna Jenkins", "Robyn Fenty", "Royal Brown"],
        answer: "Robyn Fenty",
        region:'Barbados',
        description: ``
    },
    {
        id: 20,
        type: "multiple choice",
        question: "What did Mandalorian fans name “The Child” in the Disney+ series?",
        options: ["Yadel", "Gorgu", "Baby Yoda", "Jar-Jar"],
        answer: "Baby Yoda",
        region:'U.S.A',
        description: ``
    },
    {
        id: 21,
        type: "multiple choice",
        question: "Who created the viral “Renegade” dance on TikTok?",
        options: ["Liza Koshy", "Charli D'amelio", "Annie LeBlanc", "Jalaiah Harmon"],
        answer: "Jalaiah Harmon",
        region:'U.S.A',
        description: ``
    },
    {
        id: 22,
        type: "multiple choice",
        question: "Who was the first African-American housewife on “The Housewives of Beverly Hills”?",
        options: ["Garcelle Beauvais", "Eboni Williams", "Cynthia Bailey", "Kandi Burruss"],
        answer: "Garcelle Beauvais",
        region:'U.S.A',
        description: ``
    },
    {
        id: 23,
        type: "multiple choice",
        question: "Who was Matt Lauer’s official replacement on the TODAY show?",
        options: ["Ann Curry", "Hoda Kotb", "Savannah Guthrie", "Stephanie Ruhle"],
        answer: "Hoda Kotb",
        region:'U.S.A/Egypt',
        description: ``
    },
    {
        id: 24,
        type: "multiple choice",
        question: "In 2020, Netflix aired a reality show that required participants to remain celibate. What was it called?",
        options: ["Saving Grace", "Enjoy, But Not Too Much", "Too Hot To Handle", "30 Year Old Virgins"],
        answer: "Too Hot To Handle",
        region:'U.S.A',
        description: ``
    },
    {
        id: 25,
        type: "multiple choice",
        question: "Which tech entrepreneur named his son X Æ A-12?",
        options: ["Elon Musk", "Larry Ellison", "Mark Zuckerberg", "Jeff Bezos"],
        answer: "Elon Musk",
        region:'U.S.A/Canada/South Africa',
        description: ``
    },
    {
        id: 26,
        type: "multiple choice",
        question: "What was the name of Meghan Markle’s lifestyle blog before she married into the royal family?",
        options: ["The Catch", "Brave Waters", "The Tig", "Adventures of Meghan"],
        answer: "The Tig",
        region:'U.S.A',
        description: ``
    },
    {
        id: 27,
        type: "multiple choice",
        question: "Which hard seltzer did America face a shortage of in 2019?",
        options: ["Michelob Ultra", "Truly", "White Claw", "High Moon"],
        answer: "White Claw"
    },
    {
        id: 28,
        type: "multiple choice",
        question: "What is the name of the alternate dimension in Stranger Things?",
        options: ["The Dark", "The Upside Down", "The Other Side", "The Plunder"],
        answer: "The Upside Down"
    },
    {
        id: 29,
        type: "multiple choice",
        question: "Who was the first African-American man to achieve EGOT status?",
        options: ["Will Smith", "John Legend", "Jay-Z", "Common"],
        answer: "John Legend"
    },
    {
        id: 30,
        type: "multiple choice",
        question: "Who played Rachel Zane on the legal drama Suits?",
        options: ["Zoe Saldana", "Nathalie Emmanuel", "Zoe Kravitz", "Meghan Markle"],
        answer: "Meghan Markle"
    },
    {
        id: 31,
        type: "multiple choice",
        question: "What is James St. Patrick’s nickname on the show Power?",
        options: ["Ghost", "Shadow", "Midnight", "Don"],
        answer: "Ghost"
    },
    {
        id: 32,
        type: "multiple choice",
        question: "Which popular rap artist’s real name is Nayvadius Wilburn?",
        options: ["Lil Uzi Vert", "Future", "Lil Wayne", "21 Savage"],
        answer: "Future"
    },
    {
        id: 33,
        type: "multiple choice",
        question: "Who was the first person of color to win a Grand Slam title?",
        options: ["Althea Gibson", "Arthur Ashe", "Ora Washington", "Serena Williams"],
        answer: "Althea Gibson"
    },
    {
        id: 34,
        type: "multiple choice",
        question: "Who is the most popular celebrity on social media (with the most fans on Facebook and Twitter)?",
        options: ["Beyonce", "Oprah Winfrey", "Rihanna", "Alicia Keys"],
        answer: "Rihanna"
    },
    {
        id: 35,
        type: "multiple choice",
        question: "Who was the first female athlete to be featured on the cover of Sports Illustrated?",
        options: ["Florence Griffith Joyner", "Jackie Joyner Kersee", "Sheryl Swoopes", "Althea Gibson"],
        answer: "Jackie Joyner Kersee"
    },
    {
        id: 36,
        type: "multiple choice",
        question: "Which black comedian holds the longest run on Saturday Night Live?",
        options: ["Kenan Thompson", "Chris Rock", "Maya Rudolph", "Eddie Murphy"],
        answer: "Eddie Murphy"
    },
    {
        id: 37,
        type: "multiple choice",
        question: "In which U.S. city is the show “Martin” based in?",
        options: ["Chicago", "Detroit", "Kansas City", "New York City"],
        answer: "Detroit"
    },
    {
        id: 38,
        type: "multiple choice",
        question: "Who has never been in a Tyler Perry movie?",
        options: ["Alfre Woodard", "Taraji P. Henson", "Regina Hall", "Gabrielle Union"],
        answer: "Regina Hall"
    },
    {
        id: 39,
        type: "multiple choice",
        question: "Who did Jada Pinkett-Smith reveal she had an “entanglement” with?",
        options: ["August Alsina", "", "", ""],
        answer: "August Alsina"
    },
    {
        id: 40,
        type: "multiple choice",
        question: "Who was the first Black female gymnast to win a gold medal at the Olympics?",
        options: ["Gabby Douglas", "Dominique Dawes", "Betty Okino", "Debi Thomas"],
        answer: "Dominique Dawes"
    },
    {
        id: 41,
        type: "multiple choice",
        question: "What TV series is credited as the first weekly series to depict a Black woman in a non-stereotypical lead role?",
        options: ["Girlfriends", "Julia", "227", "A Different World"],
        answer: "Julia"
    }
    // ,
    // {
    //     id: 42,
    //     type: "multiple choice",
    //     question: "",
    //     options: ["", "", "", ""],
    //     answer: ""
    // },
    // {
    //     id: 43,
    //     type: "multiple choice",
    //     question: "",
    //     options: ["", "", "", ""],
    //     answer: ""
    // },
    // {
    //     id: 44,
    //     type: "multiple choice",
    //     question: "",
    //     options: ["", "", "", ""],
    //     answer: ""
    // },
    // {
    //     id: 45,
    //     type: "multiple choice",
    //     question: "",
    //     options: ["", "", "", ""],
    //     answer: ""
    // },
    // {
    //     id: 46,
    //     type: "multiple choice",
    //     question: "",
    //     options: ["", "", "", ""],
    //     answer: ""
    // }
]

export default popcultureData;